### M. IHZA DEPRIAN

# College Student of Information System | Mobile Developer | Network Engineer

Malang | +62 853 4598 8798 | ihza130502@gmail.com | github.com/ihzadeprian1305 | linkedin.com/in/m-ihza-deprian

#### **SUMMARY**

A College Student on Information System Major in Brawijaya University who enthusiastic about Mobile Development for the last 1 year, especially on Flutter Mobile Framework and Native Kotlin. As a College Student, I am successfully creating some Mobile Applications and Application Programming Interfaces (API). I have good motivation for growth and learning new things and able to work in a team or individually.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## SMK NEGERI 1 TENGGARONG – Tenggarong, Kutai Kartanegara, Kalimantan Timur, Indonesia

Network Engineer (Maret 2019 - Mei 2019)

- Create networks for USBNBK
- Do maintenance on existing networks
- Build a Server PC

### **ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE**

### HIMMASI (HIMPUNAN MAHASISWA SISTEM INFORMASI) FAKULTAS VOKASI UNIVERSITAS BRAWIJAYA

Staff of Communication and Information Center Department (October 2020 – March 2022)

- Design Contents on HIMMASI Instagram Account
- Become a Staff of Event Division of Internal and External Sharing Session HIMMASI (2020)
- Become a Deputy Chief Executive of Internal Sharing Session HIMMASI (2021)

### **EDUCATION**

### **UNIVERSITAS BRAWIJAYA (2020 - Present)**

Associate Degree of Information System - GPA 3.9

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Mastering Flutter 2.0 : Build Travel App by BuildWithAngga
- Full-Stack Laravel & Android Kotlin by BuildWithAngga
- Full-Stack Laravel Flutter: E-Commerce App by BuildWithAngga
- Memulai Pemrograman Dengan Kotlin Certification by Dicoding from Professional Academy (PROA) Digital Talent Scholarship (DTS) 2022
- Belajar Fundamental Aplikasi Android Certification by Dicoding from Professional Academy (PROA) Digital Talent Scholarship (DTS) 2022
- MikroTik Certified Network Association (MTCNA) by MikroTik
- Olimpiade Jaringan MikroTik-APJII 2018 on Regional Level by MikroTik and APJII
- Olimpiade Jaringan MikroTik-APJII 2018 on National Level by MikroTik and APJII
- Olimpiade Jaringan MikroTik-APJII 2019 on Regional Level by MikroTik and APJII
- Olimpiade Jaringan MikroTik-APJII 2019 on National Level by MikroTik and APJII

### **SKILLS**

- Flutter
- Kotlin
- Laravel
- Firebase
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Linux (Debian & Ubuntu)

- Computing
- Networking
- Communication
- Detail-Oriented
- Problem-Solving
- Teamwork